<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sarah Blommaert</title><link>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sarah Blommaert</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 18:24:25 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Happy Powell, Happy Market</title><link>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 18:24:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-5/</guid><description>Fed Chairman Jerome Powell had a speech on February 1st regarding the interest rates and the Fed&amp;rsquo;s outlook on future rates, as well as other interesting points.
Interest rate was raised by 25bp, instead of the 50bp that had been projected end of 2022. This lower raise was due to consistent lower inflation data. Powell made it clear that the Fed won&amp;rsquo;t raise interest rates aggressively as long as inflation is under control and keeps going down; they still aim for the 2% inflation end-goal.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin back to $23k! What's been happening?</title><link>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 21:10:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-4/</guid><description>Bitcoin ranged for about 7 weeks in the $15k to $17k range. I remember back then everyone and their cats were screaming &amp;ldquo;8k Bitcoin coming!!&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;3k is the bottom&amp;rdquo;. You know when sentiment is that negative, to buy buy buy! Cheers to everyone that managed to go against the flow and do so.
But what now, how did Bitcoin go to 23k so fast? Two things to look for: funding rate and Binance futures orders.</description></item><item><title>Wen Bull?</title><link>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 16:06:55 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-3/</guid><description>To cut to the chase, no one exactly knows for sure, and anyone that tells you otherwise is bluffing.
Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss when one can expect or speculate a new bull market instead:
The cryptocurrency market has been following a 4-year cycle for the past decade. Bitcoin had 3 bull market years which are 2013, 2017, and 2021. In general, we have 3 years of bear market and 1 year of bull market, the latter usually following the Bitcoin halving year.</description></item><item><title>Is cryptocurrency a scam?</title><link>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 20:00:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/post-2/</guid><description>Is it a scam? Will I lose all my hard earned money? Some would argue that yes it is a scam and you would lose it all, others would argue it isn&amp;rsquo;t and you will make life changing money. Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss this further:
Anyone can create a token, having an appealing website and great utility, pay for marketing, get lots of hype, only to rug and make many lose their money.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:23:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.sarahblommaert.com/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Hello world! I am very excited to start this blog. I am excited to share my thoughts, experiences, and insights with you.
On this blog, you will find a wide range of topics that interest and inspire me. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s fintech, macroeconomics, cryptocurrency or technology, I am always looking for new ways to engage with my readers and provide value.
I hope that my blog will serve as a resource for those looking to educate themselves and get to know more about cryptocurrency.</description></item></channel></rss>